Joe. What's wrong? Hold on. Joe, are you okay? You need a heart? Oh. Not to like, not to eat, but to like, listen. Yeah, gotcha.
It's me, Minky. Come on up. Hi, Katrina. How are you guys? Yeah, it was an interesting, it was a good day. I had a bit of...
I went to Samans and then like 40 diamond was like he was like 40 diamond. She was like talking
Hey, there you are 30 diamond. I'm where you mad at me. What's going on?
But I did say if I did say something like offensive, I'm sorry, you know, sometimes I'd joke and it's not funny
I know I'm sorry, but I didn't mean to offend you. I really do want to
Support your your pronouns and all that
Yeah, okay over here
Um
No, you're okay, you're like fuck psyche is off to the ground. She can go eat
Here's a fish tacos and
Gentlemen, I mean gentlemen. I'm being quiet. Oh, okay gentlemen tonight. Yeah, I'm actually going to be okay
Are you okay?
Um, well, Christine gave me a clock clock me. So I wanted to come up. I wanted to leave with a bang
You did that was quite a bit
The cat with wire, but she's spreading a very false narrative about me, but it's okay
Wow, that's really lazy. It looks like the wind you're blowing out of the wind blows you away, baby
What blow my scarf up for you? Yeah
That's a Marilyn Monroe moment, you know, you're like Marilyn Monroe when the skirt blows up psyche. Come on. It's
Like the fact that she's trying to say that I trick men is ridiculous like
Say you trick men. I'm saying you trick
How did I trick you?
That's what you did. Yeah, right there. And I was like, wow, that's a nice rack
I broke up the next day. I broke the strap on my shirt when I did that. I broke my I broke my strap like right here.
When I did it.
Hey, funky.
I'm just chilling out.
I like parma or whatever, but I mean, I feel like the pink strap still work with my shirt.
So, you know, I would, you know what? I like the pink strap. I just would like was wearing them.
I wish like, oh my God.
Yeah, I just...
Hey, Paige!
I wanted to go out with a bang, because I got clutch.
I wanted to go out with a bang.
Yep.
You know what, in my recovery, I am in recovery.
I haven't porn bombed in two months.
I'm in recovery, OK?
In my defense.
Are you recovering from waking up yesterday
and realizing you're actually a guy who has porn bombed in two months?
Hey, Joe.
Yo, you're right, I should have showed my dick in.
Yo, you're right, I should have fucking pulled my skirt up
and had my tits out.
Damn, I shouldn't have pulled my dick in today.
I should have.
I don't want to throw you on, Clarity.
I don't want you dare to throw me on.
But you know what, like.
Like this, uh, you know you like there's like a lot of I think homophobia in this community and it's like so important that it's like people
Addressed it because there's so much. There's so much also like under the radar stuff going on and there's people you know
There's guys that would never have been a conversion
Telling a man I didn't have a pussy when I was out working
Yeah
She was just on Samans and then she got she kicks off the panel
You know what I got for my camera, but I can't even talk to this guy
I'll come on.
But no, like Sam had me talking about this guy's friend for the time.
Thanks.
How good of a guy friend am I, Joe?
Yeah, I got two of them too, but unlike you, I don't wear a blouse.
Yeah.
Oh, baby, you know what?
But you know what?
It's also like, it's also like one of the, it's a hard community.
It's a hard community to come out and it's like, it's like, you know, because there,
you know, there are some people who are just like, so apobic.
It's like, what are you in a horror movie?
Like turn your fucking light on, dude.
No
If he kept me telling the trick that I was trans he did recap me saying that actually to a trick
I'll throw my camera on it. This is not gay at all. If all these guys like bearer choose to stay a man turn it to women
They'd be the ugliest guys you ever saw but at least 40 diamonds like
Yeah. Yeah. She's she's she's
beautiful. You know what? Like
I'm going to change my shirt
though because I'm tired of like
my strap being broken and I'm
not. I need to my my strap
broke and I don't like that my
strap broke. What's the page?
Yeah, I put up my I put up my strap on someone, you know in a broke
Balls will be showed this very night. Not right now. It's like
Right back stage
You have to go it's me in backstage before you you're in this road, Joe.
I will take that headset you're wearing and shove that microphone up your sexy ass.
Well, I don't really like stuff up there, but I'll try with you. Hey, what's up?
We were twinsies, but my straps are working.
You be the bottom.
You're not thumping a big dog.
So you be involved.
So there.
We'll be on top.
We were twins. What the hell?
Yeah, it's not so funny.
Yeah, it's funny.
That is a convenience.
That is such a coincidence.
It's the cutest outfit.
Did you see it in blue there, too?
Yeah.
I wanted to sell them no more.
Yeah, I know they're gone.
I didn't order mine online because they didn't have
my size in the store.
Yeah, I needed to get it signed down
because it's great to do something
Yeah
She goes do you know I have that outfit too
Isn't that funny nice
I own this out in a blue also and in black. I don't I don't have it in blue or black, but I have it in that hot pink
I love the hot pink. I have a favor. Um,
Mr. Monkey, tell your boyfriend Justin next time I see my
most lap is fucking Joseph. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. No, he's
not going to see that. I got the same kind of ready, man. I'll
tell the camera, Bob. I'll behave, Joe, behave, Joe. When you
came on the show, you said you were going to be a gentleman
tonight. What the fuck happened? I lost it like two
seconds. I'll tell you, I'll tell you, I'll tell you, I'll tell
Hello, oh my god, there's a gentleman. We're in a funk. Hello, flirty. I love it.
I got my little pink purse now.
That's so cute.
That is so cute.
She goes in it goes in his in his Ravens out. Oh, I love it. You're adorable
I'm mad about the strap, but I'll fix the strap like tomorrow because I need by
Like thread not pink because the strap and it's white actually
Yeah, sorry, I'm like, do you have this outfit to come up here?
The regular man hair is blowing in the wind.
Hey, I'm not even wearing my extensions today.
I'm kidding.
It's like, I like, I'm just saying.
Here's a guy.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Oh come on that's that's what Jackie Marlin would say. I'm so mad. We could have literally been twins right now in the course. Did you see what I did on Sam?
We're gonna do it again in the future. Did you see what I did on Sam? No I didn't. What happened?
Um, Sam was really happy to have an argument with my boyfriend and like I got clapped by Christine so I kind of went like...
And in the meantime, my fucking strap broke when I did it.
Oh, it broke for a good cause to put on.
Not only did I not want to be recapped
with my argument with my boyfriend because I regret what I told him that life,
but she clapped me.
She clapped the star of the show.
I was going to be the star because I was going to be the star of the show.
Devin Devin, so he's officially your boyfriend now. You're you're you're eating
That fucking song shake your man. It's actually thing that how I take your man. So
You're just your stuff
Joe you're really bringing down the vibes
No, oh, okay. Hey, hey Joe don't you want to take a break? We're having a we're having a fun night. Yeah
Joe Joe, so you move your micro a picture microphone show and it's called granddaddy perp. Oh
Granddaddy perp right here by this call. I have a couple of this one's called
No, it has some flying monkeys and space walker
This is here. This is a goat. It's called mile-high and it's a great
Hey, let me show you your psychic. I'm gonna show you my package. Yeah. Let's see it.
Say I love goats.
Yeah, I know you do. I do too.
Granddaddy perp.
Did I ever show you my goat tattoo?
I saw it but I want to see it again.
Yeah, I'll show you.
I got a frog. I got butterflies. I got um a playboy bunny. I got a tramp stamp that says daddy's pretty sad.
Was that a real tattoo, Spongy? Showed it tattoo again.
Yeah, it's a real tattoo.
It's a real tattoo. How would I put it back on? I have a ton of tattoos.
Guys, so yeah, I'd like to go
Not showing through your fucking shirt because when I was wearing it
Let's see
Are you wearing a bra actually? Yeah? Yeah?
Okay, my nipples pop through that fucking shirt, and I have them pierced too, so they really pop out through the fucking shirt
So I'm here like how is this bitches fucking? Yeah, yeah, I have a strapless bra on
I was like how the fuck is she not how how yeah
Victoria secret has the best strapless bras for big babies
But yeah, it's like machine gun nipply that's what the fuck I'm looking at
Okay. Oh, okay
Hey, nice tats. Okay. I thought you'd be like it was like nice. I was like, do you like it?
I see the nice cat
Thank you
Yeah, I like your area. I'll be right back one more time. I'm working on getting covered eventually. We'll see what happens
I know I have a tattoo of my
You have a tattoo psyche of what?
Well, I got you know, I got a I got a BKG test here with like Lenore's face on it, but
No, that's not beat on my back
Okay, so he's talking about and Nicole Smith was on Howard Stern and then like his
producer Benji. Yeah, he pretended to be like in love with Anna Nicole. And she's like, oh,
you keep Benji. And so they finally made a date. And then it's like, then after the show, he like
went to her hotel, she never came down to the lobby. She just blew him up.
Remembering date at Lisa Jordana? Yes, I remember.
Hey, Secky, are you into like the juju stuff? Like, is there something going on in the
universe now where like the energy is really crappy?
Yeah, it was just summer it was just a summer solstice and it's like all like always in like
right around this time it's like summer time and it's like that's when all this like really
like the sun is most powerful and it's like all these people like it's like the ego goes up and
a lot of people a lot of things they keep like a lot of stuff fights and because the sun is the ego
you know so it's very about but the cells and stuff so it just seems like the vibes are weird
I'll turn on my camera.
You're going to be scared, but you've got to take a look.
You're going to look at it.
You're going to have a horrible egg with a hat on backwards.
That's what you're talking to.
You're talking to a thing.
But I think there's a full moon.
Joe, I like it better when you pick on yourself.
It's kind of funny.
Oh, you know what?
I like it better when you shut your fucking mouth.
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey.
Joe, Joe, I mean.
Calm down. Okay. Yeah
Yo, yo, you're scared. Have a time out buddy. Count to ten.
Yeah, we'll just take a minute show. I'm trying to talk to her about the about the yeah, yeah
It's like it's just weird lately like everybody everybody they come into contact with
It says here in cancer season we were in cancer analysis the energy now
calms down as we come in out of the head and into the heart out of thoughts and into our emotions perhaps you already feel it softening a
Pulling inward and emotions rising to the surface be felt reduced and healed because the cancer is ruled by the moon
And that's better like the moon is very similar with water emotions, right?
And you know that's also the cycles
So the shift is not just emotional, it's energetic, spiritual, even cellular.
We're releasing the urgency of mental overdrive and stepping into a gentle rhythm,
one where the nervous system can reset, the heart can take the lead.
As the energy turns inward, it invites us to simplify,
to come back to what truly matters, and to reestablish a deeper connection
with our bodies, our intuition, our emotional truth.
Yeah, I think that's- Well, this will end well.
I think that's part of it and then I think that also we have just stuff
Father people in the world and people are
He didn't like I kicked him up for a second
You're not fine. You're fine Joe. Hey, Dave
Little nosy
like a little nose. Yeah, I got to trim her little eyes again. She can't see. Oh, she's beautiful. Oh,
here. Oh, this guy never comes out. He's coming for you. Oh, oh, don't stop. Say hi. This is me.
Oh, look at being a little diamond on the space. Like a little diamond. He came from like this.
Breeder and they were like like top champion showcats and he got disqualified from being sold as one because of that
Good
To be touched he's a sweet boy, baby. He's a good boy
Oh
Oh my god
We saw his whole booty hole. Oh my gosh. I mean
So I couldn't tell the difference like I really couldn't tell
No, come
Well
Vloggers, I don't think I don't know I really like don't like to look at it. I mean, I don't
Yeah, I don't think I don't like
We're not supposed to be friends or acquainted with our buttholes.
We're supposed to be strangers with them.
That's why they're in the behind where we can't see and they're ready for a boss.
All right, Pam.
Now I don't feel mad.
Um, so I had my, my live driver was fucking reading the Bible to me earlier.
Oh Jesus.
He was listening to like a Bible radio and then he was like,
I'm going to read this out loud too.
No, no
And he just read it and I fucked up because it was a fucking roundabout ride where he took me to the shop and then took me back home
Oh, no, I was just like
You're miserable. I'm very sorry
But here's a twist get this he asked for my fucking number at the end. Oh
Oh, I'm sorry for your diamond. You got timed up by Christine. Oh, I'm sorry. Oh, yeah
I'm sorry. I'm just taking a piss. I tried to mute myself when I take a piss. I'm not a rude guy
By now you can hear it. Well, you got what you want. Hey Christine
Christine
drizzle like a little rain storm
So I put a fucking
I don't have a pink dress, but I wanted to play dress up with you girl. Oh, yeah. Yeah
Okay, you do you
Pinky pink is my color. I got all of it
Yeah, well you guys like blonde, you know blonde I think blonde women like look cute and pig
I don't know. I mean, you know remember like
Who's the baby spice? She's like
Blonde looks good with the pig. She also did baby blue, which was beautiful on her too like with that fair blonde hair
God, I miss the spice girls. Yeah, you actually have dye blonde hair. I like real blonde hair
Well, sorry that I can't provide that Joe not you page. I'm sorry to fucking us funky. She has fake blonde hair
They've had natural beautiful hair
Well, Joe, you know, you got to do what you got to do
Sometimes I do people get old and her hair turns gray
Smell her hair. I'll take a little sniff
Well, let's see. Oh, okay. We have good times joining the show
Good times. Hello
There were many good times
For a day or two because I showed too many firearms
I heard I heard that happen. I heard that happen. Yeah, it's like, you know, all these people say they're gonna show up to my house and fuck me up
Yeah, they're war
Hey
No, no, it's in God can be in life. I love you. I love you pretty mage. Oh
Uh-oh
Furry page. I don't think page is that furry that's kind of weird
Sorry page
Yeah, the new funky the new friend of the show she's really really awesome. She's super
I got a new headset today because my old one is crashing.
Cool.
Throw the headset.
Okay.
It's the same one that I was wearing, but it's not broken.
Oh, yeah.
I got to deliver from Walmart.
Sorry, buddy.
I'm sorry to talk, Spongy.
But give a shout out.
Give a shout out, you piece of shit.
What did he say?
That person just said something really stupid.
Oh, OK.
So hold on.
He's just back.
You can say stupid stuff all the time.
Whoa, look.
Thank you, baby.
Oh, baby.
Wow, beautiful.
It's looking so good on you!
It's looking like it got some gold on it!
He was a sexy woman!
Aww, love it!
We should have like a fashion show panel with some time pagey. Oh very nobody ever gonna look that good
That's patient her golden
Why would I want to just say about
So good times did you
Get down to show the fire you've got some firearms in your stream early. So I so I am like
Yeah, but yeah, so I know like it wasn't my stream I did I'm beat us. Oh you did oh
I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't
I don't know. I don't know.
No, okay a community warning like one or two days and then you go live again. It's not
What? No, I'm not gonna meet you. It's like
You piece of shit psych when I fucking join good times. I love it
So don't get your channel struck good times because if I had my
Because she
Okay
Okay, what's that good? So I know that I know
Give me a minute Joe. Okay. Okay. So I'm just gonna let all the pre-rectors come down
I'm trying to tell the story. So I don't try to in my class year. He showed like a cave. What's that? No, not a case
They were
MR 15 or RS SR 15, but
You're allowed to show guns
I was told that it was like you can't aim it at the screen and then it's like then I went back and I read the TOS and it's like you can't even have a show of firearm on the on the on the live if you if you use firearms it has to be like a pre-recorded video
So I'm talking I see he's still talking in the back state. I'm I'll let you on when you calm down
Give me a thumbs up. He'll calm down. So I mean thumbs up. He's liking me thumbs up. I see okay, okay
If you want to fuck around with guns you have to upload it and it has to be pre-corded you can't do it live on streamer, right?
Yeah, I'm an interesting to you as it's interesting to see what actually like YouTube does like a lot of stuff people get away with
Oh my god, yeah, yeah, yeah, I saw the idea. Yeah, yeah, I'm fortunate that
Yeah, but
They're also gore bombing where people will like they'll put a computer graphic
Yes
Good times you gotta shut the fuck up sign down the site good times was
He let people like chew up. He's not Peter, but even being though like a magnetic Joker
Good times let them all
Legend
You better blow good times the kids right now
I don't know if Joe shut the fuck up.
Good times. Everyone's been telling me.
Good times. Everyone's been saying they're going
to the big party at your house tomorrow.
There's no party.
It's a joke.
It's a meme.
I bought my plane ticket already.
I'll be there tomorrow.
I'm gonna cancel my flight.
I'm looking like my house.
I'm firing a walker out in the woods.
We're here on bonfire.
We love it.
I've got my I've got a hundred dollars for my ticket on a you know, he's uh, he's goofing me say I have to
Yeah, no, it's me. It wasn't me. It wasn't me. I'm saying you're safe frauds. Okay. Hey, we have. Okay.
Who is this person? Hold on. What are you saying? Hello?
Okay, that's just too weird. Okay. I can't be I use it back to your basis. Yeah
Okay, okay, well, I don't think anyone's gonna get arrested over all of the day. Hey, uh, what is it? Hey July 4th Frank, but
No, but you know, if you're not streaming much more, you can cast me at my show. I'm going to be
Yeah
Anybody this cat know how old it's America's birthday how old is America?
What'd you lie for? That's how old is America guys? Oh, it's like 150 years old here
A hundred and fifty to like two hundred and fucking forty one or something. Oh my god. Thank you. I love it
This is for tomorrow guys
And I'm optioning them off after the life or Canadian
Okay, I'm auctioning off
It's a red blood the flag it's the American flag
It's clear, it's clean
Big name big name says
Oh, it says E date, no stupid, uh, E dates, no stupid show, stupid show, so this guy is mad back
stage, he says this is a stupid show. Okay, well, big next, big next, what's wrong with you? Hi, sleepy.
How was your day going? Is it any better?
She was about an hour and a half away from me.
Okay, he's having a bad show.
Yeah, I would you would love that I mean
Yeah, I'm really mad that I never met a doll.
I don't know. You're mad about something.
I think you just need to get laid.
You're like so crabby.
Yeah, yeah, we don't talk to Joe before he's always...
No, the first time I talked to Joe, he was actually nice to me.
It was crazy. He must have been on drugs.
I was right. I love him more so much.
You were one time, Joe, the first time I ever met you.
You were nice.
Who the hell is that?
That is sexy.
Who the fuck is that?
I've been on a chocolate.
She's Canadian and she's white.
Hi, Bench.
Okay, what's up?
Hey, you're so good, oh, sorry.
There.
What?
Okay, that was for easy, you're so beautiful, sorry.
Oh, what?
Is that me?
I didn't see you.
You know, I said, Joe said that, Joe said.
I have to live with her for two years and they'll give me residency and then after that I can apply for Canadian citizenship. I can hold dual citizenship.
He doesn't want to marry you so you can get citizenship. They're romantic.
I don't have to marry you, I just have to live with her.
No, she doesn't want. She doesn't want you to move in.
No, she probably had a problem with her.
Hey, good time. Good time to talk to her.
Talk to her about it tomorrow at your party.
We're all flying in.
There's no party.
Yes, there is.
Okay, no, right there.
There's the only party.
The only party.
Okay, and honestly, we're okay good times. I love the country area. We're basically I'm sure hey our man
Is it safe good times downloads sims again? He would be we should be worried for okay?
Hey, okay
Yeah, he's gonna move in instead
Yeah, I don't want to live with another man again as long as I
Just have a room and I never leave
Okay
It didn't sound very nice.
All of us can make a compound mate, it's like beta in a year.
Why don't you guys all just be down here?
You guys can all just marry one.
All of us are animals.
Wait, guys, wait.
You can all be keeping the insistence with me on my farm.
Yeah, we'll make a compound on the farm.
I want to make a compound.
I want to make a sex cult.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Uh, what I mean, I really it's a true crime. And so I've probably seen a bunch
I've seen is like a interview with a Heraldo and I've seen but not too much. I mean, I think he's kind of like
Not pretty appealing. I don't like them. You're coming across like Charlie a little bit. Well, I was I was joking
I was called a satire. I really do not win this very compact or 30
Okay. Yes. Yes. Okay. I mean, I was not funny
Was maybe not been funny, but I was trying to
Sorry, fine. Yeah, I have a
Your mind is like not working right I shouldn't complain, but
I mean, let me take I mean, I'm adjusting up for you Joe. Can I try that?
He's doing that. That wasn't it
But now when you order a vera had like this bigger to like John Wayne Gacy's like
like great
He's like we're going to open it. We're going to open his cup like that.
It was Al Capone. It was Al Capone.
It was Al Capone's secret vault view.
I know. I know.
It was Al Capone's hotel.
And there was nothing in it.
There was nothing in it.
That's what I'm saying. There was nothing in it.
They waved through the whole hours like wait till you see this.
They opened the doors like wow.
There's nothing in you.
It looked like an empty wine bottle like is this Pages living room like an empty wine bottle Christ
I've seen this before
It's gonna be empty very soon as I love that it's gonna be empty soon enough
it doesn't stand a chance
at least fate is real
that's why I love being up there
we're real people
unlike good times
I'm wearing overalls
dumbass
I like
she seems like a nice person
she's beautiful
oh she's better than me
she's better than me
I know you're not gay. I know you're not gay. I don't know that. I don't know that he's not
Hey, hey, I think that's maybe one of the reasons they guys hit on you
I'm so abruptly here is because they were trying to prove that I'm gay because I'm on the pale
So they have to like
We gotta prove we're real men. We gotta prove we're not homo
I can prove the page I'm not gay okay okay okay that's enough
You're gay good start it's not okay
Calm down it's like everything's calm
I don't know I don't know what you're gonna do
We already had an incident this year
I think it's a big part for the band baby
It's a big part for the band
Why would he? Oh, never mind. I remember. Yeah, well, he played he played a song for like three hours and
Yeah, they put a curse on me a hex and then he you know said he was
Cursed, yeah
Uh, let's say he said he's any curse me. He said he put an ax on me. Mr. Big pipe
the
I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I
just random just any time any time it's a new trivia stream oh my god no it's gonna turn into a
fucking new string good time okay guys let's work right we're having fun let's have fun
what part of the body grows at a rate of three millimeters per month a toenail
a nail a nail a nail a nails yes it's fingernails
Yeah, that's what I meant to say.
Black, Black Forest is originally from which country?
Black Forest?
Can you read the question again?
No, just for a second, we can't hear.
Are you fucking cake comes from where Germany Germany Alaska North Pole the fucking South Pole
Okay, hey, hey Joe yours qualified because you're being too annoying
Okay, what superhero sidekick is known as boy wonder Robin
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
The rivers I'm not sure
No, we'll chat get it. Let's see
Let's see. Let's see big folks figure the secrets you get on
Yeah
I did use these questions
Okay, okay, the Colorado River is the Colorado River loser set loser
Good job. She's ready, but not everybody heard them. So just go with
So which state is also known as
The volunteer state like in Nebraska, that's hard. I've never volunteered Missouri
Tennessee per month
Where is the tennis hall of fame that was the joke
Where's the what
Where's the tennis?
Joe stop
The tennis all day Wimbledon Wimbledon Alan Jackson Alan Jackson. No
London so I said sweetie said London. No, okay
Hey Bader
What's the answer? We give up. We give up. It's Newport, Rhode Island. Okay, I'm going to say it's 245, I'm going to say it's 245, I'm going to say it's 245, I'm going to say it's 245, I'm going to say it's 245, I'm going to say it's 245, I'm going to say it's 245, I'm going to say it's 245, I'm going to say it's 245, I'm going to say it's 245, I'm going to say it's 245, I'm going to say it's 245, I'm going to say it's 245, I'm going to say it's 245, I'm going to say it's 245, I'm going to say it's 245, I'm going to say it's 245, I'm going to say it's 245, I'm going to say it's 245, I'm going to say it's 245,
I said it and you but I heard I know that I have no idea. That's weird
Petunia Petunia
Oh my god, you got a
question.
of Greek mythology. It's a
joyous squeezer. joyous
squeezer. No, it's not.
The valley of the moon your anus your anus on the moon on the moon Arizona, you make me go
China China the valley of the moon the valley of the moon
It's in China. It's in Japan. Where's that pretty short China China
No, it's like super far away from that
And Jupiter Jupiter Mars meeting us. Yeah, Marjorie, Marjorie, whatever
Jordy said
It's in Jordan, okay, it's in Jordan
Which artist had more hits?
The question is this trivia. Sorry about his age and question again. You know, yeah, she got it. She got it
Please let's page answer questions. Good times. Don't be fucking rude. What country is directly west of Spain?
Portugals
There is there is no country west of Spain you dumb woman. I'll see you tomorrow good times at the party at your fucking concert
I'll see you tomorrow, buddy
Bye Joe, I'm not gonna talk to you at the party tomorrow. Just call me a dumb woman
You better be that party
Name from mid-evil Italian words or sorry for bad air black play great work great work
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
I mean guys
We treat you guys
It's a
I think was a TV show. It was a TV show. I remember watching that was low kid. Okay, that makes sense then. I didn't.
The show is creepy as all hell. It's malaria. It's malaria. Malaria. Bad air. Mal area. That makes sense. Yeah.
Oh an ominous dish in is studies. What on Oh ma Mastis chin. Yeah
Yes, oh no
Words, but it's like language lingual like I'm
More vocabulary. Is it a fear of something?
Oh no, I'm on a Pia
I'm out of here
Names it's the origin some of you said the origin of names. Okay. Yeah entomologists
Well, it's not well. No
No, yeah
Oh
So what
Proceeded the iron age bronze
Yeah, holy fucks sake.
That was good.
The sage was before the Iron Age, alright?
Well, fuck God, it was before it did.
It was before it did.
Who is pictured on the first adhesive stamp?
a friend or big war big war war war war war war war war war war war war war war war war war war war war war war war war war war war war war war war war war war war war war war war war war war war war war war war war war war war war war war war war war war war war war war war war war war war war war war war war war war war war war war war war war war war war war war war war war war war war war war war war war war war war war war war war war war war war war war war war war war war war war war war war war war war war war war war war war war war war war war war war war war war war war war war war war war war war war war war war war war war war war war war war war war war war war war war war war war war war war war war war war war war war war war war war war war war war war war war war war war war war war war war war war war war war war war war war war war war war war war war war war
Okay, Ben Franklin's like Ben. Why don't you say Benjamin?
Yeah, you're still talking about bronze and go good times kiss. Oh, okay. So what is dire straights 1982 album called?
It's called my cock
Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. Let's see. Let's see like sure of you with this page, you know page and
And the chat
Good times in Joe. It's like a little bit inappropriate. We have like we're doing a fun little studio game. It's being so inappropriate
I mean, it's just like what are you? Are you 12 years old?
Well, I don't want to get them stop eating. You can put these hater on page every second the tree will early and show
You're just being loud and obnoxious and we're trying to hear the questions and answer
Okay, I'm gonna give you guys one minute one question timeout that I might bring you back on if the ladies agree
So did you nobody answer the question yet? What was the?
What is Dire Straits' 1982 album called?
No clue.
I don't know.
That's not the name of the album.
Good times day.
It was his cock.
That's not the answer?
No.
It's not the answer.
Good times day.
That was not the answer.
It was not funny.
Nobody laughs even when I parody the show.
Thank you for kicking good times.
Oh, you're welcome.
I'm going to bring him back in a minute.
It's called Love Over Gold.
Oh, okay. Yeah, um, so you guys I hope you get this one cuz like I'm gonna love whoever gets this
What is Canada's motto?
The different if free and die
Okay
Um, it you know, I guess it's
I know I do
Under the dollars right? What is Canada's motto?
Oh Canada, oh Canada, oh Canada, how beautiful you are. Canada rules. Yeah
Uh blame Canada
American page we're so focused on America. We don't know anything about
It's from C to C
Okay, I'm C to C. Okay. Yeah. Okay. C to 70 C
Which Bill Bill in which Bill in broke Batman's back
So
Two-faced
Was an Ivy Catwoman
Okay, who was it vain
All right, Bane I'll give Bane credit Bane. All right. I'm not stupid. You should marry me
No, shut the fuck up good guys. I'm talking about with your good
What was the first domesticated bird
It was the parrot. No, all right
It was a a flamingo
Canary canary
Yeah, so if you talk to choose are from
Astrophobia is the fear of what the stars under water
Thanks fear of snakes
Astrophobia asked her as you are as you are for me. It's a question again, please answer question one more time
If you don't mind. Hey, she's doing it Joe
Astrophobia, astrophobia, yeah, that's what it's
The fear of flying, the fear of flight, the fear of flight.
Well, let me ask you a question. What's the fear of checking your mailbox?
The fear of good times, the fear of good times. Oh my God, that's scary.
No, that's actually a real thing.
What is it? Good times. Really?
Postalphobia.
There's actually a phobia where you're scared to check your mailbox. Yes.
Wow.
Oh, is that because real bad bills?
Okay, well, I don't talk about bombs, okay, so anyway, it's lightning and thunder
Oh
Yeah, I didn't know that either
What is you you scare me
Because you think you're so smart
Man, I didn't come up
One day this scares me out good times if he's like I'll let my cat out at six in the morning
And you don't even check on his cat. He don't fucking love his cat. He's a fucking cat
Well my dogs in heaven cuz all dogs
Person
It's called androphobia
Yeah, you know that right off the bat.
Y'all have an anthrophobia.
I hate that guy named Andrew.
Andrewphobia.
Why would you be afraid of men?
You can just beat their ass.
No, I'm just afraid of you good times
because you think you move your grass
like nine times a week
and there's only seven days in a week
but you know you're good at something.
I just wish Peyton's shirt
would just drop down a little more.
Thank you.
I'm sorry about that.
That's what I'll stop it. Don't pay me to what I'm talking about. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay.
October, July, July, July, July for guys.
August, September.
Thank you.
Here.
September.
No, you're the fucking awesome woman. How dare you talk to bays like that you piece of shit
Yeah, well, I'm serious why you're so fucking
Well, yeah, was that a piece of cheese fucking Santa Claus dude that came on calls all weeners the other night
No, you remember let me ask you a question psyche. Stop rolling your eyes and rolling your lips
Cartoon hold on
Remember the cartoon of frosty the snowman when he was like getting like he was all hot in the greenhouse
And he's like all frosty about it. I try but I'll see that
Well, that's Christmas you're talking about boys. Okay
Okay
I don't hear anybody. Oh my gosh, you know, who's in the backstage. Oh, it's your friend. Oh well
Well, you formed on me at least three or four times. I'm sorry, you know, I would love to have you on again
But I say I don't want to
Upside page
Yeah, well Joe doesn't shut up so I couldn't say anything
Nice to meet you spunky hi
Okay, I lose audio is bad
Yeah, yeah, so Joker's here for Paige and psyche. Oh, thank you. It was me spunky to the less funky and
Joe Joe Joe just scares me with like what he's like how about his movie his mouth I say it and like
Just chill. I mean it's like you guys won't calm down. So I'm gonna let okay. Well, we're done with trivia, right? That was it
When Joe comes back on I'm leaving. Okay when Joe comes back there we go
He may be drinking like I don't okay Joe. Oh, yeah, so wait
Joe happy back with spunky leaves, okay?
He requested that you she like not have you here. I'm just gonna say she's causing me physical pain
And I do have middle finger and then okay, I don't want it. I don't want to get married. I don't think
Well, you know Paisley has a love for you know human beings. Yeah. Well, she's the one you ogling at her
Oh shit, sorry funky. He's flexing. He's flexing. I couldn't help it. I'll take a minute. I'll take a minute. He's flexing
Do you actually do math or what?
What a rude person. What a rude person. I mean
Hello, yeah, who's Vicky, what's Vicky saying?
Come on up Vicky, what are you showing now Joe? Oh, he's looking at his shirt. Oh
He knows the game where diamonds go a diamonds
got
Kicks for 24 hours
So maybe oh, what are you doing Joe? Joe is like covering yourself a flower and
He never he never like will lips is like he never like lifts up his shirt all and he was doing it backstages now
Trying to
Yeah, who told you about this trick because LD tell you that I can just like come on come on the show naked
I'll probably let you on
Hey Jenny, girls, ends it, and Spongebob is cute.
Yeah, Joker says Spongebob is cute, of course, but yeah, Spongebob is all cute.
And Vicki says, hey, no, why don't you be in the chat?
Oh, okay
Earlier in your little stream someone had mentioned that Jenny girl Jen Jen was having a bad day and now I see her in here
She won a record. Yeah. Well, Christine had mentioned that but also it's like up to her, right?
And I also psyched they don't just like take over. Yeah
But Jenny we just want to say we love you and I hope your day gets better
Jenny and Jenny's really awesome. It's like, you know, I think
I feel like, you know, she's a lot of good in the world and she'll be returned to her.
It's like, I think, yeah.
Thank you. Thank you. My name is Howard sir. Oh, thank you Joker Joker. No, that's a great compliment for me
Yes
I don't think he was I actually like that's like I've always said like he's been my Howard sir has been like my inspiration for the show
I've also had like his produce is Howard sir producer. Surely he braided my show once I've also had Wendy from Howard sir on the show and
Man a few other people
That we're from a show is one of his producers. I just wanted to get a reading from page after holiday. Yeah
After holiday. Oh, yeah
Sorry for the noise behind me. Can you guys hear my cats meeting the shit out of a jingle ball? Oh jingle balls? Yeah, there she goes
Yeah, they are like losing their mind over this toy. Yeah
Well, my cat was sleeping on speedos. I think the
And it is like crack
They are losing their minds both of them are playing with it at the same time and they're just batting it around from each side of it
It's really cute
That is so cool
Like I love little cat toys. My cats get bored with toys very quickly
But then they'll find you know, they love like little mice like little mice toys and like
Chill in on the cats this little box is anything new they're very they're very snoopy. They like to snoop cats are the biggest snoops
Oh, yeah, what's that?
So that's like what's in this like you know that you look kitty use your cameras on stinky
We want a porn pan bomb over. Yes. Thank you so much. Thank you in the chat. Yeah, stinky is the chat. Oh, is she in the chat?
Yeah, how'd you know she's backstage? I'm here in the chat. How'd you know she's backstage easy?
Yeah, yeah, Noel's back in a backstage Noel. Have a talk in the chat. Okay. Fuck in the chat because I don't want to see
I already stopped for a pretty done. I already already form bombs the one tonight. I don't I want to see you form up
Oh, she's not looking happy. Okay
Stay in the fucking chat Noel
We'd like to see my backstage like who's backstage. They're like the angriest fucking people with them
I'm sorry guys
On the show. I mean get them. Okay. Well, you're
Say something real fast a side of a tweaker is somebody that goes like this then they rock back and forth and this is exactly what you fucking do, man
Okay, how is that just a sign of anything else? I've always been rocking back. I've looked out my videos and it's like I'm not enjoy
And I do rock back and forth sometimes
You're a tweaker. You're a tweaker. You're sitting in that. Okay. Bye. You're sitting in that chair. You look like you're 50 pounds less than me
You're wearing overalls and I'm sitting there like a hick. Okay, so it's off heating on page and go away
Okay, and okay. Okay. I had to lose some problem. Yeah
So everybody has like little coping things like little like nervous things everybody has them right and a lot of Tourette's
I don't know Joe Joe you can't come until spanky or spunky approves. No, well
I think you're banned because you form bomb you too many times and
Then you like laughed about it and then you and Joe, I don't stop don't play your middle finger at me
Don't put your middle finger at me
This is like
This is stupid shit, but we love it. Yeah, you know what? It's it's really good time most times
It really is this is like light-hearted good fun psyche, isn't it? Yeah, that's what I try
Oh, yeah, so Joe Joe
You don't insist apologize you want apologize
Joe you better not say that you do not say anything about that. Nope. He said one second. Okay one second
Okay
First and foremost, I do apologize like that's what I I don't need you got it
You don't got to eat what I'm talking to you ain't got to be chewing on your fucking food
But the second point I want to make is
Like if you go to ban good times, I'm like better than
He left let me call the smelly or what's her name? Squirty. Let me tell her name is her name is spunky
Okay, okay, no, it's not gonna work. Okay, Joe. She's not interested. She's not
Hi stinky stinky and spunkier and like somewhere names
I know well, you know, if you I don't be met stinky her name is Noel and she's
Cool person like when you know, she we're having fun like until she started form bombing me
Yeah, and it's like it's not like it's not like whoa, you know where you diamond desert like whoa look at those big boots
It's like
Okay, I won't say anything. I'll just say it's just it's it's it's interesting. Vader is actually quite
interesting that there's like such a wide variety of personalities on here like I would never do that to
you, Psyche. And then there's people who just want to show everything anyway. Right.
Yeah, I know you would never do I mean the people like most people would never do it because it's like the only reason
You would really do it is to try to hurt the show or just maybe to be shocking for everybody
I respect you in your show, and I want to keep it going. Yeah, I know it's like people that it's like
I think I'm platformers for everybody to like I want everybody to come here
Everybody you can be old fun and have a good time. Have a few giggles, right? Yeah. Yeah
And so I just have to be a little bit stricter with the rule.
I don't like, I kept having them back.
I mean, they were like so rude, but they're kind of like,
almost trying to like be funny, but they weren't funny.
It was, it was kind of like, yeah.
I just was, I don't know.
If Joe was funny, you know, he wouldn't be such a headache,
but he's just not.
He misses the mark.
It's up.
Yeah, well, you know, I think he's he's not backstage anymore. No, well, no, no, that's very sad
But no, well, I just can't I can't trust you. No. Well, you look you did inform on me three times
I canceled my stream all that all the time is gone. Okay
So, Hannah, I know what I'm saying.
Spunky, can I call you mom on YouTube?
Oh, that's, oh, that's, oh, that's,
oh, that's her.
It's stinky, isn't it?
She's in the back door.
Yeah, I'll be your mommy.
Maybe you'll meet a friend.
Maybe you'll meet, he meets Spunky like later, you know?
But, um.
Yeah, maybe Noel will be my friend.
Okay.
Good, I think yeah, let me let me go. I mean I can like put up the banner which is here
9-Ball said hashtag not happening. Oh
Yeah, there you go. Not happening. Oh, it's okay. Maybe you maybe it will
Should I be friends with stinky? Okay
Good luck with that
Well, okay, I'll put up the banner and like I'm gonna say hello, but I'm not gonna you can't be on for real long
You just so you can say hello. Okay. Hello
Your microphone's not on oh well
No, I'll
No, my baby girl
Hi
Hi, how are you?
Yeah, how how was your day?
Okay, are you okay? You're not kind of sad. Just a little bit pissed off and just a little bit
Tired. Are you mad at me?
No, just a
Something else. What else what happened?
Just in a another panel like I'm not gonna say here like
They have set you something bad happened on that show. Yeah, honey fuck them. I'm sorry. You don't feel good
Well, don't let it get you
Yeah
Fuck them move on
Did they let you on or not or they or was there a bad bad experience or they were mean?
It was on Sandy's channel. Okay. What happened?
They were going out there her friends and her and there was a clip those two
Clips and yeah
So what about them?
Okay, are you too sad right now? Okay. It's okay. I don't know who Sandy is or any I just wanted to see if I could get a quick
Quick synopsis, but like you're here now. So why not? You know, you're on the show. You're oh, there's a straw
Oh, that's her straw. She likes to choose straws, right? I might rock back and forth and will choose straws
We all have her thing right she plays with okay, so I don't know Marcy. I think she's gonna behave, but I got I'm watching I'm watching
Okay
We're so SUVs equals. Oh subs home. You know, well that has 700 subs that she doesn't even have it
Yeah, I've seen her she's last year before she does like a she does like a
Special Special Olympic basketball or something. It's like some kind of special team
Wolfie's nickname is repulsive. Oh
What happened
That's how big spider working on my he said back state. Oh, what happened beta beta what she said back state. Oh, let me look
What happened I don't understand what's going on the TFO you got mail. Oh, oh, you got mail, okay?
Okay, Marcy. Yo, I saw her on jayce. Oh jaycees. So that's candy
So what happened on what happened vicky museum if the interesting or anything you can write put light on the situation
She's not really
explaining. Oh, just to announce someone in chat. Oh, sorry, sorry. Next stage. Well, she told you to take
to, oh, oh, she did.
I don't lie to myself. That's not very nice. No, I didn't do that. I don't think she would do that.
I forgot about it. A lot of people tell me that.
Really? Suckie? Don't ever.
Well, no, that was the first thing that Q said to me, and uh, you know, I don't know. People have
You know in a roundabout way, I think that society is really it they really like would like to people to do that
And you know, so they don't have to have blood on their hands or something. It's like so they try to like
Make some people do that crazy. No, well randomly shows her boobs. Yeah, I know she's done it here three times
To get rid of this guy. He's emotional. Who's which guy? Okay, the chat is distracting. So how are we doing?
So we know well, yeah, what are you okay?
Hello
Okay, well, I'm gonna give her some time. It sounds like she's using some time off with the panels for a little bit
It's just you can just chill in the chat. There's a lot of nice people to chat. No, okay. We have Tom
Oh, okay
Charles I have to ask you what do you enjoy about tweaking? What does it make you feel good?
You were talking to Charles in the chat. No, no, your name's Charles Manson. I'm talking to Charles Snyder. Oh
Charles Manson
No
Well, I don't know and I haven't talked a lot about my drug history
And I don't need this been talked about
How much we can just acting normal
You saw what you saw a woman you see if you told me to ask you to stop a woman or 30 times
I think says ask him about the woman. He's talk a woman
It is your name page. Charles, where's your thought process go to when you get confused?
It goes to, well, am I crazy or are they fucking trying to make me crazy? That's what I'm saying.
Easy as me, five racks. He spelled my name wrong once. Yep. How do you misspell Brian King? Good
I'm gonna sit down with that. I'll go up here. Hold on. I'll put this monkey there.
I've very rarely seen somebody just tweaked out on fucking methamphetamine before. It's fucking weird.
Oh my gosh. This guy is projecting. Is this guy projecting guys?
I've seen people walking down the sidewalk thinking they're scuba divers.
And you're fucking about as tweaked out as they are, motherfucker. All right?
Shock him. Okay. Anyway, there's anything else to say. Are you are you allowed to like fucking take chill pills?
Are you fucking on like what the fuck you're what is your deal Charles?
And they get me confused with someone else
Well, no, I don't have any confused with anybody. You already said that you thought you're Charles Manson. I
Said what what do you talk? You're you're speaking words in my mouth and making shit up
I remember
You said on your stream thought you're Charles Manson. You're gonna start a call
Tonight I'm not a Snyder motherfucker
Okay, you're doing an interview like a hard-hitting interview. Okay, Tom. Okay. Well, your brain is all over the place
I'm looking at your eyes. You can't even fucking focus on a thought
Guys
What are you doing? Jesus.
You told me my special needs
Charles, what what do you get
about starting some weird call?
I was joking. It's all a joke.
I'm asking a serious question.
No, what I said was a joke.
And so what you're asking is like,
you're like, like I was serious
when I was saying it as a joke.
I don't know how much about that video tonight, Charles.
None, okay, none.
But Spunky was saying that she would like to, you know, if Page were going to start a compound
like in Canada, I was like, well, I want to start a compound and I'll start a sex cult.
But I was just kidding.
It was a joke.
Nobody laughed.
Nobody laughed in the chat.
Nobody laughed in the camera.
I'm actually, I'm being here now.
So everyone took it serious.
We're going to believe it.
I'm just mentally retarded.
Yes, I should be.
Oh my God.
House Mike
Wow guys, okay poor two people on the chat. Awesome. Okay, he's
fixing that. Okay. She's not even showing
Before my fucking I get I get fucking horribly insulted over my goddamn nails in my fucking shirt again.
That's why I came up here to tell you about my dream with page
Okay, what was it what happened to drink? What was the dream? I?
Didn't say I said it was the dream about I had a dream with page last night
And it was so real because all my dreams are so lifelike
So either this YouTube shit is getting to me or the interaction though
You know how the brain works and whatever dreams mean so last night had a dream
It was me page
Let him finish his dream. Hold on. Um, I was fucking we were in my backyard like at my house
There was me in page and someone else behind us
But she was there for some reason and I wasn't questioning it like why is she here? It wasn't like we're she just was there
We were there and then I kept like flirting with her right and like like just fucking will not creep you
Shut up. And so I'm telling you a dream I had
And then you're selling like a creep. All right. You just ruined it now. You're not gonna know the rest of the dream
Later
Your backyard or was it good time back there? Maybe if you're man with a barbecue tomorrow
I ripped off ripped my barbecue down
Yeah. Okay. I'll leave. I'll
leave you. That was a weak ass
troll. Who me? No, no, the
guy that you just had on. That
wasn't Alex. I mean, he's you
know, he's a troll. Uh I said
Marcy. Yes. Okay, Juan. Uh
I'm going to call our princess page. I don't give a shit. Okay. How are princess page?
Princess page.
Okay, what are you thinking about about Charles? I'm sure I'm sure women love
pet names from men they hardly know.
Vicky, you've been getting many chance to cross love channels. Yep.
I mean, I give her no, well, that's why you say that men and women are not supposed to like each other Charles
No, they're I just put they are supposed to I mean it's like, you know, they're you know, but there's certain
Types people are attracted to you. We're supposed to like each other, but then men get in the way
Get in the way that's real that's real the fucking question Charles
And then again the way I don't know I try not to get I try to stay in my lane as I say, you know, not really go and bother
Princess page
Okay
You hear you hear you hear the silence or is it like you're in comfortable silence? She knows I'm joking
You're laughing you're you're laughing because it's like that'd be a good sign
Laughter silent. I heard silent. I heard silence and an uncomfortable pause
Okay, grant good times makes an avatar in a video game of a woman he stalks and great. Oh my gosh
Did you make an avatar of some woman you stalked good times no, I know that's not true
Okay, it's a me. It's a mean that you said fucking making joke about or something. I'm not making a joke about I'm wondering someone says
Oh, yeah, the avatar game. It's not true. It's okay. It's not sure. It's not true. Okay, but this is from home
Who said that it was?
already time
30 times that is that that's where you diamond
Are you dating story done?
He's on me. Yeah
I'm not a fucking queer faggot. Okay. Okay. Okay
Let's calm down easy
Can't read some of the comments come in the comments or just know a little bit crazy, okay, okay
No, are you okay? What's going on?
Well, I think she fell asleep
I'm moving looks like she spoke see how what she wants to say. All right, so
I think she fell asleep when I was gonna get back at Brian King
Okay, I'm up. You're just gonna sit there and do a death there. Oh
It's like your profile shit, okay, I'll be fine easy time to copy shop
Okay, good time to get it create a sims character of Rip Royce and installs
They have that oh my god first. I don't think they have that
It's a it's a meme joke that they like to make okay. No, we have a spell on Amanda Erickson
Yeah, yeah, you know, I'll just hang on the chat. I think you'll help more fun in there
Okay, I know I know I know you're pissed off. It's better to be in the chat with people in the chat about it
Okay
Person does two minutes. Okay. Yeah easy go ahead in a month. I'm gonna
Take care of stuff, okay
Yeah, so your mom and Chad that would be stinky or spunky. It's our spunky and that's she's right there, right?
I think I think it's your mom and you know, thank you say where's my mom in the chat like
Okay, was he yeah, she's in the chat. She's fine. You enjoy your meal
I saw you show your legs and your tats now I want to fuck you in more
Where's Justin was was all boil is he there not loving you
What do you mean he's at his house? Don't you guys live together? No, we don't you don't live together
I'm in there
Make your move
Okay
I do want to say
Crazy
No, I saw you little poodle that can't see
Alright, yeah the poor thing I see you have a nice kid you got $50 take that thing to the groomer and do the right thing
Man, you catch you're killing
She just wait it's only been like 10 days and her like I had to
Like I know
This is like shaved down
I'm gonna see that puppy in the groomers tomorrow
The doggies they can't do it for themselves
We'll lie on
How long does work 24 hours
Like
Your microphone is loud and it's all the way up and the echo cancellations not even on
of
Yeah
You can fucking take your own nails off like some dental floors
There's ways look it up on you to rip them off yourselves
You know shine down like like all women like women used to do the real women. They do their own manicures
Like what
What's going on?
I like girls to take care of themselves.
You understand those little Barbie girls?
What the fuck is going on?
Like girly girls.
Oh my god, lipstick.
Are there actors on here?
Okay.
Guys, guys.
We'll have a nice night.
Who wants to drink another beer?
You better get another beer, you fucking drunk ambassador.
I am drunk as shit. I almost stumbled into the wall. I'm being quiet
Your beers are in your fridge, right? They're in your fridge. You have to go in here, right?
Why are you laughing?
Joe I'm not laughing
That's why he's insane they do
Now you're right. Don't worry about it. But you know what? I'll I'm not a bitch if the Orioles suck at least
I still love them even when they when they're doing good
You got a man. I was with them when they stop
I bet you
Oh, is that Alex? Is that Alex? Little Alexander?
You've had too much to drink.
Alex is alright. I like Alex. He's a very good guy.
You see, I'll be quiet. I apologize. Okay. I thought I was being quiet. Damn it. I can tell by the look at her.
I love you baby. I'm sorry to be being quiet.
I see I see like I see like a look of like fire.
No page isn't the best thing that ever happened. I had a dream with her last night.
I was trying to tell you guys, no, I got caught off before I even started, so I'm going to keep it just for me, and if I ever meet Paige, I'll talk about it, or if we're alone or awkward, that's it.
I'm not sharing with you assholes, and that's why that happened. It wasn't meant to be shared with you.
Don't you even put your hands on Paige. Don't you ever say Paige's name.
I did last night in my dreams.
She'll not say her name.
Well, hey, we all had dreams. I dreamed about Paige. I did too.
guys, stop. Noelle's here, they had it. Noelle, let's indulge her.
Noelle! Fuckin' late this week.
Sorry.
Oh, I thought you were right.
Okay
She like she showed her
No
Oh my god, it doesn't fucking who the fuck is that next to you that no, well
of the
the
Why are you pretty sure?
Yeah, why you got to get old good time a little standard on YouTube where women can't pull out their tits but men can
Yeah
It's a different
Panel that's why flake is a good panelist. He knows how to run over gang sign
Hey guys
She was doing something you would she say it's that language
I believe she said shut the fuck up like
No, she was saying I'm about to poem bomb you
the
Oh, hold on
There's a whole group of people on YouTube where they only speak sign language to each other
They just like
She makes tons of
I don't know who at one normal person that can be you
That was a great take time
Now you're going too far
I can't say anything bad
You can talk to that
What the fuck are you rambling at Alex?
What the fuck's so funny you, bitch?
The fuck's so funny, Alec?
Don't you ever fucking laugh at me?
I'm laughing at his old dude in the middle with his overalls.
Oh, I'll show you the middle, boys.
I'll show you the fucking middle of it.
I'm laughing at Joe Chippley,
for the more all-real fans.
Just talk about my voice like in good times.
One more time, and I'll see you, boys.
Don't talk about my voice like in good times,
or I will see your fucking end.
It's funny. It's funny.
That's funny, Joe.
It's some farmer from hell.
Wait a minute, what else found you?
You're looking better than ever, baby.
Oh
And then I melt they melt my heart these two I don't take no
a transition
She is she is pretty I'll give her a thank you
I had a dream with her last night and it wasn't perverted
I was gonna share with all of you until good times open his big fat mouth
And I woke up like damn
What do you think this dream meant but you didn't even let me tell you the dream
Okay
all you've ever in your arms
I don't think so
yeah
keep it PG
there's a lot more to it
what else was it you remember
if I was ever drawing at the bar
and actually met a woman that was just looking at page
I'm like what the fuck
you're actually back to me
it's YouTube shit it's getting to my brain
I had a greener face
I never had a dream with anyone on YouTube
in two years out of all my
two
Alex is so loud and he insulted me last night and made me really sad
That's the point where I had to go
Alex, Alex did
I'm in Rondo, I'm in Rondo
Yeah
And then
I remember
Because he's me
So then why did he have a nice dream about me?
That's
Interesting
I'm asking you guys that exactly I don't know
My subconscious is she was she thinking of me and infiltrated my dream like what like
no okay so it's not that so why do you tell your fans it's like Alex why do you tell your fans it's like
I mean I told you that I wanted to go there
Alexander you made me really
he's a good fucking guy and I want to tell you I want to tell you
I thought you were dressing in the dream we were making out
oh my god I'll just I'll just go from where it started because it was like a long interaction
and then uh
then we started like we were we got together and we were like making out and it was it was weird
you want me to tell you the whole fucking dream? oh yeah
tell the whole dream
tell us the dream give us the dream alex tell us the dream
You know what's the end in my view?
Yeah, yeah, pay attention to the one in here.
Pay attention to the one in here.
Just don't tell, don't tell it.
Don't tell it now?
What the fuck?
Tell it or don't tell it?
No, keep it to yourself.
Keep that sexy dream to yourself, big dog.
Keep it to yourself now.
Yeah, tell it.
it wasn't provided it was not it was just like go ahead describe it like a house court i don't know
so we were in the backyard she was there i was there there was two other people there another
person left me in jail put in the dream check this out it was so weird i woke up tripping
so then there was just me and Paige and someone behind me
and i was like just we were in the yard and i kept like flirting with like talking we were like
laughing bantering and i was not listening to this i literally remember in the dream thinking to
myself fuck it i'm gonna kiss her i thought that to myself in the dream and i just grabbed her and
pulled her in and kissed her
on the lips and she kissed me back I didn't know what to expect almost like on a real
like life date like I'm just gonna kiss this bitch right now so I pulled the ring I kissed her
and it was like a good and she kissed me back and then we just started like making out and then
after that I was like oh my blondie and then I remember bringing her in the house and just like
I just brought her in and she was like I need to use the bathroom and then all
a sudden it was like this golden palette and now there's the weirdest shit on her
I'm like why did I like our Alex's wet dreams
We didn't have sex we just kiss
And we both wanted it and what happened when it happened
but that's my brain
page party wants to throw up right now
that's why I just want to answer
it's a youtube
it's a little chubby cheeky
hey are you doing Freddy Krueger in his dreams
or is he just having fun
I have read your page bro
and she was in my back office for some reason
I pulled her in, I kissed her
and we started making out
And the story was weird, right?
I never had a dream like that with Summer.
Better talk it out.
It's been one or any other girl on here,
and I met a lot of women on YouTube in the past two years.
So I think I was feeling guilty because I love Paige.
And I hate calling her the B word,
just like I do to Christine or any other woman up here.
but this is a different world to me
I don't walk around in the real world calling women bitches
You see, I come from hell on YouTube
and my mind's still wide that way
No, it's not
Like you people are not the same as real people in
Me anyway
It's a whole different world
So there's definitely a little like
But the guilty thing psyche doesn't make sense to me because I call everybody a bitch and all this shit
Making a
I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know page one people dipping into their energy about
your you
Please see it. Please turn your cam off for safety. Good times. The hundreds that record it. Oh, oh
You're recording
Okay, well
Person seems to know what they're talking about
Fucking women are not bitches. They're beautiful creations of God. I agree. I agree. You know God
Got first God created man, then he had a better idea
Alice is so insecure or so insecure just here for attention. Oh, I'm gonna say he didn't say your
Good times. I don't know. It's like if I was like, you know
I like my car broke down on a farm and then there is like just it was just like good times on the farm
Okay
People call
Okay, well, there's everything. There's nothing new under the sun. So guess what like you missed my first stream yard today
I'm sorry
And I got my cat or my PayPal thing figured out the link too
Did you good times were you at the pages live
No, well, no, no, if I don't know where the channel is
It's great page in wildflowers. No, it's not
Yes, it is
Okay
I don't think so out. I don't think so buddy
who are you talking to right now?
you are talking to my friend
hello yeah
hello i'm talking to you so i can be my best friend
yeah what's wrong god
are your headphones be any bigger
god are you calling like uranus
nice headphones god
could your mouth be any bigger
wait a while
can your chips be any bigger
they could if i made them bigger
who's
I just don't like skunkie you can tell me like Joe you don't like skunkies your tattoos are fucking
I
Call it call it you guys call them call them call them John
Yeah, okay
All right, so we're in theory, so my dream, we're in theory.
Okay, Alex, Alex, you just think you're just kind of a stupid dream.
We're here to figure it out, right?
Well, I'm in love with the girl, I'm in love with the girl.
Yes, yes, yes, you're in love with her, you're in love with her, you're in love with her, you're in love with her, right?
You gotta figure it out, Alex.
I'm in love with her, I'm in love with her, I'm in love with her, I'm in love with her, right?
I'm in love with her, I'm in love with her, right?
I don't know. I don't. I don't
don't know. I don't know. I
those
Yes, you have a vagina something else in the vagina. It's okay if you do out if you're like
let's be let's be real you might you might have any you might have any objections though
but my eyeballs like to look at her my eyeballs like to look at page that's all i'm going to say
i'm not being rude i'm just saying my eyeballs are not related to joe
oh you just said it on the camera it's not to do with the eyeball
joe stop being so cute joe there's beautiful women like rice everywhere that's my pro
i love her price
I mean, yeah, she's not, you know, she's not ugly. She's a beautiful girl, but it's not that.
I scared her. You're saying I scare Alex
Oh, you're fine
Readings on my channel, so I'm gonna go do that for a little while. Okay
Guys you can go if you want to read it from a page. Go check out our channel, a prayer page, a wildflower, a series of cards, a series of cards, a series of cards, a series of cards, a series of cards, a series of cards, a series of cards, a series of cards, a series of cards, a series of cards, a series of cards, a series of cards, a series of cards, a series of cards, a series of cards, a series of cards, a series of cards, a series of cards, a series of cards, a series of cards, a series of cards, a series of cards, a series of cards, a series of cards, a series of cards, a series of cards, a series of cards, a series of cards, a series of cards, a series of cards, a series of cards, a series of cards, a series of cards, a series of cards, a series of cards, a series of cards, a series of cards, a series of cards, a series of cards,
the
So you guys like me now
If you're a love of tajas go get in the big line you see over there, okay? That's what you have to do, okay?
Station's beautiful because that's like
she knows
she doesn't let me see what I say she's beautiful
well I don't talk with dogs
I'm not going to tell you anything about it
but yeah that's the funny dream I had
I just wanted to share with you
and I'm not saying that
you're not bad as this
you're better at spinning off faster
I've had so many weird dreams
like big time said
they don't mean shit right
dreams are just dreams
go inside, go inside
Can do this like you're on
You're actually gonna take my friends like go fuck yourself you fucking suspender wearing little bitch
Well, it's either Matt. They're an extreme form of attention
Like you're fucking so 20 of them you fucking
the
I don't know what I'm talking about, but I don't know what I'm talking about, but I don't know what I'm talking about, but I don't know what I'm talking about, but I don't know what I'm talking about, but I don't know what I'm talking about, but I don't know what I'm talking about, but I don't know what I'm talking about, but I don't know what I'm talking about, but I don't know what I'm talking about, but I don't know what I'm talking about, but I don't know what I'm talking about, but I don't know what I'm talking about, but I don't know what I'm talking about, but I don't know what I'm talking about, but I don't know what I'm talking about, but I don't know what I'm talking about, but I don't know what I'm talking about, but I don't know what I'm talking about, but I don't know what I'm talking about, but I don't
So you still have a hairline kind of you're stupid. So you're going to hear
I heard you were showing weapons on your channel
Oh, you're gonna have another universal weapon?
Take it off right now!
What is he doing? What is he doing?
What is he doing?
Well, that's dirty.
It's dirty too.
They look muddy.
30 years
Where's your washing machine this is a question I'm asking everybody
How open do you go to the laundry bag or do you have a washer dryer in your house?
I have a washer
You do in the house?
I have a washer in my house
Anyone that has a washer dryer in the house has got it
Well, I have one in my closet, I open the door, there's a washer dryer, without that, fuck life.
That's the first thing I say.
Oh my god, it's like bitching.
It's like what do they smell like?
Just what they smell like fucking roses.
It's not like roses.
That's fages, over.
Oh, armpit shit.
Oh my god.
Imagine those armpits imagine the whip taking away for those pits. Yeah, no offense Alice, but they probably show our pierce
They probably smell like piss and shit to be honest
Joy your mouse smells like fucking
He's been wanting to see more
There's a thing called the old ladies at least fucking psych is a real man
He took a shower in his g-string there was flies flying around but he took a shower once in six months
You're supposed to take two showers a day
like what the f**k is going on?
I shower twice a day
it's not a f**k your hemorrhoids
you f**king idiot
you f**king overseas
spend away on easy s**t
spend away on no shower
and having motherf**ker
you're not your way
look at him
it's so smelly
I just smell my pants and they don't smell like B.O., so...
So who's it like, cheese the poor man?
Isn't it summer heat too?
Fuckin' cheese smellin' motherfucker.
I don't have to go mud my grass.
Cheese the motherfucker.
He palates pizzas on himself.
It's 10.02 in California, so I don't know.
Alright, so it's one for Halloween,
it's one for two for me.
Oh, you know it's like good.
Yeah, give me the courtesy what no offense. I will chop good times head off
The fuck up the times you fucking smelly motherfucker
I'm just, I'm just, I'm just, I'm just, I'm just, I'm just, I'm just, I'm just, I'm just, I'm just, I'm just, I'm just, I'm just, I'm just, I'm just, I'm just, I'm just, I'm just, I'm just, I'm just, I'm just, I'm just, I'm just, I'm just, I'm just, I'm just, I'm just, I'm just, I'm just, I'm just, I'm just, I'm just, I'm just, I'm just, I'm just, I'm just, I'm just, I'm just, I'm just, I'm just, I'm just, I'm just, I'm just, I'm just, I'm just, I'm just, I'm just, I'm just, I'm just, I'm just, I'm just, I'm just, I'm just, I'm just, I'm just, I'm just
Oh, golden shower. That's what being psych. We're talking about 10 minutes ago
I'll give a second golden shower and I'd say say go bring your mouth. Here we go
Hey, oh
My god, it's like hell raiser. This is like a horror movie. What the hell is like doing? This is cool
To where's my lights
Yeah, do it then be psyched see if you can do a horror movie. Let's see. Let's see what he gots. Let's see what he gots. I
Don't see it so far
Okay, okay, fair enough that is nice that is cool that is pretty cool
Thank you good times. That is pretty badass. I don't have anything
I just look like I'm in a padded broom and you know what?
I am in a bad way, I am in a bad way, I am in a bad way, I am in a bad way, I am in a bad way, I am in a bad way, I am in a bad way, I am in a bad way, I am in a bad way, I am in a bad way, I am in a bad way, I am in a bad way, I am in a bad way, I am in a bad way, I am in a bad way, I am in a bad way, I am in a bad way, I am in a bad way, I am in a bad way, I am in a bad way, I am in a bad way, I am in a bad way, I am in a bad way, I am in a bad way, I am in a bad way, I am in a bad way, I am in a bad way, I am in a bad way, I am in a bad way, I am in a bad way, I am in a bad way, I am in a bad way
Is that what you did? You suck my nuts, fuckhead.
Ooh, why are you being gay?
What are you fucking mad at?
That's what I talk.
Psych. Psych is actually a real guy.
Thank you, Psych. Thank you, Psych.
Fucking weirdos.
Yeah, we're the weirdos, good sides.
We're the weirdos.
You have to see what? We're the weirdos.
You're literally wearing suspenders, you old bastard.
Joey, thank God you I don't live in fucking Baltimore. All right
Wait, what would you come see me? They're not knock you to fuck
Bitch I can fucking you two suck. No, no, no threats. No threats. Oh, you're gonna fuck me now
He's gonna have sex with me. I don't
Make it just make it make it date like everybody else, you know, have fun
Everybody have fun. Yeah
No, everybody have fun
We are
Tomorrow at the barbecue at my flight book tonight
Buddy give a fucking warning
anybody that actually
say he's an asshole, he's a stupid asshole